let topics = {
    animals: [
      {question: "What is your favorite animal?", answers: ["dog", "cat", "rabbit"], translation: "Hewan apa yang kamu suka?", choices: ["dog", "cat", "rabbit"]},
      {question: "Can you name a big animal?", answers: ["elephant", "lion"], translation: "Sebutkan hewan besar!", choices: ["elephant", "lion", "mouse"]},
      {question: "How do you ask for permission to go to the restroom during class?", answers: ["restroom", "bathroom", "pee", "toilet"], translation: "Bagaimana cara meminta izin ke toilet saat jam pelajaran berlangsung?", choices: ["May I got to the restroom, please?", "Excuse me, may I use the toilet?", "Can I go pee?", "I need to go to the restroom"]},
    ],
    school: [
      {question: "How are you today?", answers: ["fine", "amazing", "good", "awesome", "better", "happy", "sad", "grateful", "great", "well", "excellent", "not feeling very well", "not feeling well", "a bit under the weather", "rough", "dealing", "not", "tired", "tire", "stressed", "bad", "trying"], translation: "Hi, apa kabarmu hari ini?", choices: ["I'm fine, thank you", "I am not feeling very well today", "I am good", "Not so good"]},
      {question: "Where are you right now?", answers: ["school", "in the", "in the classroom", "in the library", "in the teacher's room", "canteen", "in the principal's office", "in the laboratory", "in the computer room", "in the music room", "art room", "in the bathroom", "gate", "flag", "flagpole", "classrooms", "tree", "teacher", "friend", "teachers", "friends", "in the school yard"], translation: "Di mana kamu sekarang?", choices: ["I'm at school", "I am in the classroom", "i'm in the canteen"]},
      {question: "Look around you. What do you find there?", answers: ["a", "i", "u", "e", "o"], translation: "Lihat sekelilingmu. Apa yang kau temukan di sana?", choices: ["Table", "Chair", "Pencil"]},
      {question: "Touch something you see around you right now! What do you feel?", answers: ["is", "feel", "feels", "is", "are", "i feel", "i like", "it feels", "i feel something", "this feels", "it's", "it is", "i don't feel", "i don't like", "i do not like", "i don't want", "i do not want", "i can not", "i can't", "sorry", "no"], translation: "Sentuh sesuatu yang kamu lihat di sekitar kamu saat ini! Apa yang kamu rasakan?", choices: ["I feel something soft", "it feels warm", "I don't feel anything", "Sorry, I am not comfortable doing that"]},
      {question: "Ok, What are you doing right now?", answers: ["i am", "i am not", "i'm", "i'm not", "don't", "do not"], translation: "Ok, apa yang sedang kamu lakukan sekarang ini?", choices: ["I am reading a book", "I'm just relaxing", "I'm not doing anything"]},
      {question: "Oh, Are you with someone right now?", answers: ["yes", "no", "not", "private", "I am with", "i'm with", "alone", "myself"], translation: "Oh, apa kau bersama seseorang saat ini?", choices: ["Yes, I'm with my firend", "No, I'm alone right now", "I'd rather not say", "It's a bit private"]},
      {question: "Ok. Class starts soon, so let's hurry up and go to class.", answers: ["yes", "sure", "on my way", "okay", "alright", "all right", "great", "i'm ready", "go", "hurry", "class"], translation: "Ok. Kelas akan segera dimulai, ayo segera pergi ke kelas.", choices: ["Okay, let's go!", "Sure, let's hurry up!", "All right, I'm on my way!", "We are already in class."]},
      {question: "Let's begin our lesson!", answers: ["yes", "let's do it", "sure", "i'm ready", "ready", "start", "good idea", "let's begin", "begin", "okay", "go"], translation: "Mari kita mulai belajar!", choices: ["Yes!, Let's do it!", "Sure, I'm ready to start!", "Good idea, let's begin.", "Okay, I'm ready to learn."]},
      {question: "Can I sit next to you?", answers: ["yes", "no", "sure", "good idea", "okay", "sorry", "can", "can't", "can not"], translation: "Bolehkah aku duduk di samping kamu?", choices: ["Sure, I saved you a seat!", "Sorry, someone's already here.", "Good idea", "Yes, let's work together."]},
      {question: "What is your favorite subject?", answers: ["my favorite subject is", "i like", "it's", "i love", "it is", "i prefer", "like"], translation: "Apa pelajaran favoritmu?", choices: ["My favorite subject is English", "i think it is English"]},
      {question: "What class do we have now?", answers: ["We have"], translation: "Sekarang kita pelajaran apa?", choices: ["We have Math", "We have English", "We have Science", "it is", "it's"]},
      {question: "Did you do the homework?", answers: ["yes", "no", "forget", "forgot", "did", "do", "finish", "finished"], translation: "Apakah kamu sudah mengerjakan PR?", choices: ["Yes, I finished it last night", "No, I forgot to do it", "I did half. I'll finish during break"]},
      {question: "Do we have homework for tomorrow?", answers: ["yes", "no", "forget", "forgot", "did", "do"], translation: "Apakah kita ada PR untuk besok?", choices: ["Yes, we have homework for tomorrow"]},
      {question: "Can i borrow your pencil?", answers: ["sure", "yes", "can", "sorry", "here", "take", "no", "can't", "can not"], translation: "Boleh aku pinjam pencilmu?", choices: ["Sure, here you go!", "Sorry, I forgot mine to", "Yup, take it!"]},
      {question: "What are you going to buy during recess?", answers: ["i will", "buy", "want", "like"], translation: "Apa yang akan kamu beli saat istirahat?", choices: ["I will buy noodles and juice"]},
      {question: "Class is over. Are you going home now?", answers: ["of course", "Yes", "No", "am", "is", "are", "will", "shall"], translation: "Pelajaran sudah berakhir. Apakah kamu langsung pulang sekarang?", choices: ["Yes, I am", "No, I have music club"]},
    ],
    food: [
      {question: "What food do you like?", answers: ["pizza", "burger", "salad"], translation: "Makanan apa yang kamu suka?", choices: ["pizza", "burger", "salad"]},
      {question: "What is sweet food?", answers: ["cake", "candy"], translation: "Apa makanan yang manis?", choices: ["cake", "rice", "bread"]},
    ],
    colors: [
      {question: "What is your favorite color?", answers: ["blue", "pink", "yellow"], translation: "Apa warna favoritmu?", choices: ["blue", "pink", "yellow"]},
      {question: "Name a color of the sky.", answers: ["blue"], translation: "Sebutkan warna langit.", choices: ["blue", "green", "red"]},
    ]
  };
  
  let currentTopic = [];
  let currentIndex = 0;
  let score = 0;
  let recognition;
  
  function startGame() {
    const selectedTopic = document.getElementById('topic').value;
    const childName = document.getElementById('childName').value.trim();
    if (!childName || !selectedTopic) {
      alert("Please enter your name and choose a topic.");
      return;
    }
    currentTopic = topics[selectedTopic];
    currentIndex = 0;
    score = 0;
  
    document.getElementById('start-area').style.display = 'none';
    document.getElementById('game-area').style.display = 'block';
    speak("Hi, My name is Gin. I will help you talk in English. Let's Start!");
    showQuestion();
  }
  
  function showQuestion() {
    const q = currentTopic[currentIndex];
    document.getElementById('question').textContent = q.question;
    document.getElementById('translation').textContent = q.translation;
    document.getElementById('choices').innerHTML = '';
  
    q.choices.forEach(choice => {
      const button = document.createElement('button');
      button.textContent = choice;
      button.onclick = () => {
        document.getElementById('textAnswer').value = choice;
      };
      document.getElementById('choices').appendChild(button);
    });
  
    changeBot('ðŸ¤”');
    speak(q.question);
  }
  
  function submitAnswer() {
    const userAnswer = document.getElementById('textAnswer').value.toLowerCase().trim();
    const correctAnswers = currentTopic[currentIndex].answers.map(a => a.toLowerCase());
  
    if (currentIndex === currentTopic.length - 1) {
      if (correctAnswers.some(ans => userAnswer.includes(ans))) {
        score++;
      }
      showScore();
      return;
    }
  
    if (correctAnswers.some(ans => userAnswer.includes(ans))) {
      score++;
      changeBot('ðŸ˜ƒ');
      playCorrectSound();
      speak("Good job!");
      currentIndex++;
      setTimeout(() => {
        document.getElementById('textAnswer').value = '';
        showQuestion();
      }, 1000);
    } else {
      changeBot('ðŸ˜Ÿ');
      playWrongSound();
      speak("Try again!");
      document.getElementById('textAnswer').value = '';
    }
  }
  
  function showScore() {
    document.getElementById('game-area').style.display = 'none';
    document.getElementById('score-area').style.display = 'block';
    document.getElementById('score-text').textContent = `Your score: ${score}/${currentTopic.length}`;
    changeBot('ðŸŽ‰');
    speak("Congratulations! You finished the game!");
  }
  
  function changeBot(expression) {
    document.getElementById('bot-face').textContent = expression;
  }
  
  function speak(text) {
    const utterance = new SpeechSynthesisUtterance(text);
    utterance.lang = 'en-US'; // Pilih bahasa Inggris Amerika
    utterance.pitch = 1.2;
    utterance.rate = 1;
  
    // Menentukan suara wanita dewasa
    const voices = speechSynthesis.getVoices();
    let voiceFound = false;
    for (let voice of voices) {
      // Mencari suara wanita dewasa
      if (voice.name.includes('Google UK English Female') || voice.name.includes('Google US English Female')) {
        utterance.voice = voice;
        voiceFound = true;
        break;
      }
    }
  
    if (!voiceFound) {
      // Jika tidak ditemukan, gunakan suara default
      utterance.voice = voices.find(voice => voice.lang === 'en-US');
    }
  
    speechSynthesis.speak(utterance);
  }
  
  function handleKey(e) {
    if (e.key === 'Enter') {
      submitAnswer();
    }
  }
  
  function startListening() {
    if (!('webkitSpeechRecognition' in window) && !('SpeechRecognition' in window)) {
      alert("Sorry, your browser does not support voice recognition.");
      return;
    }
  
    recognition = new (window.SpeechRecognition || window.webkitSpeechRecognition)();
    recognition.lang = 'en-US';
    recognition.interimResults = false;
    recognition.maxAlternatives = 1;
  
    recognition.start();
    document.getElementById('speakButton').classList.add('listening');
    changeBot('ðŸŽ¤');
  
    recognition.onresult = function(event) {
      const result = event.results[0][0].transcript;
      document.getElementById('textAnswer').value = result;
      checkPronunciation(result);
      document.getElementById('speakButton').classList.remove('listening');
    };
  
    recognition.onerror = function(event) {
      document.getElementById('speakButton').classList.remove('listening');
      changeBot('ðŸ˜Ÿ');
      alert('Error occurred: ' + event.error);
    };
  }
  
  function checkPronunciation(userSpeech) {
    const correctAnswers = currentTopic[currentIndex].answers.map(a => a.toLowerCase());
    const userAnswer = userSpeech.toLowerCase().trim();
  
    let accuracy = 0;
    if (correctAnswers.some(ans => userAnswer.includes(ans))) {
      accuracy = 100;
      speak("Perfect pronunciation!");
    } else {
      accuracy = Math.floor(Math.random() * 40) + 50;
      speak("Almost correct, try again!");
    }
  
    console.log("Pronunciation accuracy:", accuracy + "%");
  }
  
  function playCorrectSound() {
    document.getElementById('correctSound').play();
  }
  function playWrongSound() {
    document.getElementById('wrongSound').play();
  }
  
  function sendWhatsApp() {
    const phoneNumber = "6281243635245"; // Ganti dengan nomor WhatsApp tujuan
    const childName = document.getElementById("childName").value.trim();
    const topic = document.getElementById("topic").value;
    const date = new Date().toLocaleDateString();
    const message = `Hello! This is ${childName}. I just played the English Game on the topic "${topic}".\nMy score: ${score}/${currentTopic.length}\nDate: ${date}`;
    const url = `https://wa.me/${phoneNumber}?text=${encodeURIComponent(message)}`;
    window.open(url, '_blank');
  }